[Music]
hello everybody it is nicole from
kiwi and today we'll be reviewing the
artify alcohol brush markers
that were kindly gifted to me so let's
not waste any time and hop right into
the video
the price on their website is originally
35.99
but is on sale for 26.99
and on amazon the original price is
35.99 as well
however the price does fluctuate and at
the time of recording this
it was on sale and i wasn't sure if it
would stay on sale
when this video would be uploaded
for the packaging it comes in a plastic
case with a clear top
and a black bottom there are latches on
both sides that keep the case closed
and there is a handle on the top that
lays flat however when lifted it becomes
a proper handle and you can carry the
case around
inside it is divided into four sections
and the markers do stand
straight up if they are all there
however if there are some missing
then they can fall over
as for the marker it has a white barrel
with the logo on the side
and a matte finish on one side
they included the chisel tip or broad
tip
and on the other side marked with a thin
gray band is the
brush tip the top of the caps have the
color and code on both ends
so it's easy to identify and i noticed
that when coloring
this brush nib is a little bit more firm
than marker brush nibs like
copics it comes in a set of 48
and it includes really bold colors as
well as some
grays
[Music]
for the pros i think this is very travel
friendly and portable
since the markers come in a small case
that comes with a handle
it makes it really easy to just grab and
go
i like that this marker has a brush tip
i feel like
many other alcohol marker brands have
just the
fine and chisel tip but this one
being another brush marker option is
really great for those
looking for a cheaper alternative to
the more expensive brands
i think this is a great beginner size
for those wanting to test out the
markers
and it's also a good price because it is
less than a dollar per marker
there is a good range of colors with
them being very bold and saturated and
vibrant
however that does bring me into my cons
where
i feel like the colors are so bright and
vibrant
that there is a lack of pastel or light
colors
i found it a little bit difficult trying
to figure out a color scheme
for this drawing with this set of
markers
because so many of the colors were so
bold and
kind of didn't have a range of light to
dark
overall i still really did enjoy using
this set
and if you saw my previous video i used
it in the raven and apple
video i think it's a good addition to my
collection
and it would be a good beginner set but
i feel like it's more effective
as an addition to other markers you may
own
just so you have more range because this
one does include
more bold and saturated colors
[Music]
so i hope you enjoyed the video and
found it useful or helpful in any way
if you did and want to see more videos
like this be sure to hit that subscribe
button
and ring the bell so you're notified of
when i post a new video
so with that i want to thank you all so
much for joining me today
keep drawing keep creating and i'll see
you all next time
bye i broke it
[Music]